{"Topic": "States and Boundaries", "Subject": "General Knowledge", "Data": [{"Question": "Which is the largest State in India?", "op1": "Madhya Pradesh", "op2": "Maharashtra", "op3": "Rajasthan", "op4": "Uttar Pradesh", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "How many States share their boundary with Nepal?", "op1": "Five", "op2": "Four", "op3": "Three", "op4": "Two", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Which of the following States does not have a boundary with Pakistan?", "op1": "Gujarat", "op2": "Rajasthan", "op3": "Haryana", "op4": "Punjab", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "With how many States does Delhi have a boundary?", "op1": "Two", "op2": "Three", "op3": "Four", "op4": "Five", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which southern State has the shortest coastline?", "op1": "Kerala", "op2": "Karnataka", "op3": "Tamil Nadu", "op4": "Andhra Pradesh", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Yanam which is a part of Puducherry is located in the State of -", "op1": "Kerala", "op2": "Tamil Nadu", "op3": "Andhra Pradesh", "op4": "Karnataka", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Which among the southern States is the largest in area?", "op1": "Andhra Pradesh", "op2": "Telangana", "op3": "Tamil Nadu", "op4": "Karnataka", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which of the following States has a boundary with Myanmar as well as Bangladesh?", "op1": "Manipur", "op2": "Mizoram", "op3": "Tripura", "op4": "Nagaland", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "How many States in India have a coastline?", "op1": "Seven", "op2": "Eight", "op3": "Nine", "op4": "Ten", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Which of the following States has the longest international border?", "op1": "West Bengal", "op2": "Rajasthan", "op3": "Gujarat", "op4": "Arunachal Pradesh", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "With which country does India have the longest border?", "op1": "China", "op2": "Pakistan", "op3": "Nepal", "op4": "Bangladesh", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Which of these States is surrounded on three sides with Bangladesh?", "op1": "Tripura", "op2": "Mizoram", "op3": "Nagaland", "op4": "Manipur", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Tropic of Cancer passes through how many Indian States?", "op1": "Six", "op2": "Seven", "op3": "Eight", "op4": "Nine", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Which State in the north eastern region of India is the smallest?", "op1": "Mizoram", "op2": "Nagaland", "op3": "Manipur", "op4": "Tripura", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Which State of India has the longest coastline?", "op1": "Gujarat", "op2": "Andhra Pradesh", "op3": "Tamil Nadu", "op4": "Kerala", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Sikkim shares its boundary with how many States?", "op1": "One", "op2": "Two", "op3": "Three", "op4": "Four", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which State has the boundaries with most States?", "op1": "Madhya Pradesh", "op2": "Uttar Pradesh", "op3": "Chhattisgarh", "op4": "Jharkhand", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Which among the following is the largest in area?", "op1": "Arunachal Pradesh", "op2": "Assam", "op3": "Meghalaya", "op4": "Nagaland", "Answer": 4}]}